♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return to
Deejay Butcher.
♪ ♪
Hey, bro!
Hey! You requesting a song or
ordering some sliced meat?
Meat! Half a pound
of turkey, please.
You want a sample?
You mean like
a slice of turkey,
or like a short section
of one musical recording
that's been digitally repurposed
to be part of a new song?
I don't know.
I might quit this job.
God, late-night TV
is all terrible.
Oh, we don't have
to watch this.
We could turn to channel 875
and watch Conan.
Here, let me see
what else is on.
In honor of Sammy,
on the bus ride over here,
we all sat in the back.
Lucille Ball was
back there with us,
and I saw her smoking a Cuban.
Then Desi zipped up his fly.
Whose wedding is this?
It's hilarious.
Peter, it's not a wedding,
it's an infomercial
for The Dean Martin
Celebrity Roasts.
Wait, you mean Comedy Central
didn't invent those?
No.
Well, what about funny news?
Did they invent that?
N-Not really.
But they invented comedy.
They didn't
invent anything.
Well, they centralized it,
that we know.
Man, look at these people.
They don't breathe.
They just drink
and smoke and laugh.
I want to do that.
What are you
talking about?
You want to
have a roast?
Yeah! Look, he's the man
of the hour.
Everybody loves him.
They got his picture
in a circle.
How do they do that?
Pictures come in squares.
Hey, Cleveland,
how tall are you?
I don't know.
Cadillac come up
to about here on me.
All right, so I guess I am
the tallest one of us.
What are you talking
about? I'm six-two.
Says so right here on
my driver's license.
Yeah, that-that
doesn't count.
Why not?
You're gonna
make me say it?
Lay me out
on the floor.
I'm six-two.
Hey, you guys.
Peter, how tall am I?
I don't know,
how tall is a mailbox?
You're about
a mailbox.
But listen, I-I want
you guys to roast me.
What, you mean
like they do on TV?
That's right, I want to be
the man of the hour.
And I want all my pals
to give me a good ribbing.
Can we work blue,
like Marlin Johnson?
♪ Oh-ee, oh-ee,
hey-yo, ha. ♪
Oh, you know
it, homey!
Huh, all right,
that could be fun.
Great. And you fellas
shouldn't pull any punches.
Just let me have it.
Nothing is off-limits.
Geez, Peter,
you're more excited
than Adrian Peterson
at an arboretum.
Daddy, what kind
of tree is that?
Man, I want to beat you
with so many things around here.
Ladies and gentlemen
and people who have wandered in
from the Chinese wedding
next door,
welcome to the roast
of Peter Griffin,
with your roast master
Glenn Quagmire.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you very much.
Joe, I'd tell you
to take your seat,
but I'd be
about 15 years too late.
Ha! And we're off.
Well, what can I say about the
man of the hour, Peter Griffin?
Oh, boy, here
it comes.
Well, first off,
Peter's always been special.
In high school,
he didn't play sports,
but he did wear a helmet.
All right, that's kind of funny.
Tough, but fair.
You know, Peter, I love
your chin, but I got to ask.
What's it like
going through life
with a scrotum
so close to your mouth?
You know what, hold on.
I'll just ask
your teenage daughter.
That... that's inappropriate.
You know, Peter's
challenging the stereotype
of Irish guys being fat,
drunk and stupid
by throwing "a little gay"
in there, too.
Oh, nice, homophobia.
But I got to say, the worst part
of being Peter's friend is
knowing that eventually
you're gonna have to be
the fat-ass's pallbearer.
Lift with the legs,
right fellas?
P-People think I'm fat?
But seriously, everyone, let's
have a big round of applause
for the real hero tonight:
Peter's chair.
How you
holding up, buddy?
Two chair jokes
in the same monologue.
Sloppy.
Peter's got a small penis,
but, hey, nothing
grows in the shade.
This just in...
is what Peter had to say to
his wife on their wedding night,
so she knew it was
actually happening.
Peter's so ugly,
he couldn't get raped
in our holding cell
down at the station.
For those of you who don't know,
we have a real serious problem
with people getting raped
in our holding cell
down at the station.
Hi, I'm Professor Comedy.
No!
Peter, you're loud,
you can't hold down a job,
and you got high blood pressure.
You could be a black guy if your
ding-a-ling wasn't so damn tiny.
How does everyone know?!
Peter moves his lips
while he's reading,
'cause he's trying
to eat the book.
Roasted!
You know, as Lois's father,
I hate the thought of her
having sex with Peter.
And so do I!
Damn it, Lois, you stepped
on my punch line!
Shut up! You're drunk!
Stop serving her!
I asked Peter
what he got on his S.A.T.s.
He said, "Mayonnaise."
Peter's so fat and stupid,
Lamar Odom tried to bang him.
Well, ladies and gentlemen,
now that we've had our fun,
it's time to give our man of the
hour a chance to have his say.
Please put your hands together
for Peter Griffin!
Okay, yeah,
I got something to say.
Screw all you guys!
I hope you all eat turds
and die!
None of you bastards
are my friends no more!
Brian was the
worst one.
Family, I have
an announcement to make.
Peter, we're eating.
Just tell us what color it was
and be done with it.
On account of my buddies
all being nasty sons of bitches,
I've decided I'm gonna
find new friends.
Oh, come on, you're
overreacting.
The roast was
your idea.
You asked them to
make fun of you.
Yeah, but I thought
they'd stick to material
about how I'm too handsome
to work at a brewery,
or-or how I have tiny
little baby sneezes.
I'm sure it was all
meant in good fun.
Yeah, it was supposed to be fun,
but it was humiliating.
I felt like
a premature volcano.
I just think you're a
really cool island,
and I'd like to
get to know...
Oh, God!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I am so sorry--
you're just so pretty.
Please, don't tell
the other islands.
I've been thinking.
Maybe I got to find friends who
can't make fun of my appearance
'cause they're
weird-looking themselves.
Like those two bearded dwarves
walking across the street there.
Hey, will you bearded
dwarves be friends with me?
We, sir, are
Italian children.
Good day.
Thanks for hanging out
with me.
I never thought of my kids'
principal as being a friend.
Well, "pal" is right
there in the name, Peter.
Yeah.
Hey, it's cool you got
the keys to the school,
and we can hang out
when no one else is here.
What should we do?
Oh, I got a few ideas.
Wow, I've never drank
so much milk in my life.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
What other ideas you got?
How about this second
fridge of milk?
Uh, how much milk
do you drink?
I just drink milk until
somebody stops me.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just not meant
to find a new group of friends.
Well, Peter, you're always
welcome to hang out with me.
Yeah, but I'm talking
about the kind of friend
that doesn't bark at horses
when I'm watching a movie.
Fine, fine, you want to get
trampled in your living room?
Be my guest.
It's just...
I don't know, I-I don't seem
to fit in anywhere.
All right, I'm gonna
go get some more coffee
and maybe a gross
microwaved sandwich.
Excuse me.
Can I please have
another no-foam latte?
Uh, yeah, sure.
But, you know,
I don't work here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You look just like
one of the baristas.
He doesn't look
that much like me.
I think she meant me.
Oh. Oh, yeah.
I could see that.
Hey, we should make out.
You got it, mister.
Double-foam, am I right?
You're funny.
Yeah. Oh, my God,
you're so twisted.
I'm Jamie, and this is
Becca and Karen.
You want to join us?
Sure.
Great.
We were just debating
if Jamie should hook up
with this guy she met
a few nights ago.
Okay, I want the deets,
like, yesterday.
Wh-What the hell?
Did I just say that?
You sure did.
You're a natural
at this.
Wh-What is "this"?
It's what we do!
Wow, you know,
I know I just met you guys,
but I've kind of been looking
for a new group of friends.
D-Do you maybe have room
for one more?
Are you good at talking
about how busy you are?
Because that's a lot
of what this is.
Ugh, yeah, but don't talk
to me about anything
until I've had
my morning coffee,
'cause it's like
I can't even deal.
Well, I think I speak
for all of us when I say
we'd love to have you in
our group of girlfriends.
Oh, my God,
that's awesome!
Hey, can I be the one
who laugh-screams
really loud at restaurants?
As long as you're
picking up the check.
Oh, we're gonna ruin
so many people's evenings!
Oh, boy, I'm blending
right in with you gals.
Like a panda bear
on a bed full of pillows.
I'm hiding from the zoo.
They want me to have a baby.
I don't want to have a baby!
Hey, isn't it funny
that you guys came over
for a dinner party,
and all we're doing is
standing in the
kitchen, drinking wine?
All our
toothbrushes were
in that one woman's
glass this morning.
Girls, it is so nice to
be part of a group again.
And I'm having
the best time.
Especially yesterday when
we all got mammograms.
If I have cancer,
we're all going to Brazil.
So what's for dinner?
You said we were
having Italian?
Yeah, and then I
realized I'm not good
at making
fettuccine Alfredo,
but I am good at
making reservations.
Do you get it?
Oh, God, I'm so bad.
Stewie, it's time
for your bath.
Oh, what's
going on in here?
Oh, hey, Lois.
Hey, these are
my new friends:
Jamie, Karen
and Becca.
Karen's the one
with the mommy blog,
so if you think you know her
from somewhere, that's where.
Oh, nice to meet
you all.
Would you like to
join us for dinner?
Oh, no, I don't want
to get in the way.
Besides, I got to get
this little man in the tub.
Great. Now they're all
picturing my wiener.
Oh, thank God.
For a second, I thought
she was gonna come with us.
What?
Seriously, Peter,
how do you live with her?
I know, that voice.
Ugh.
And what is that hair color?
Creamy French Dressing?
Oh, I love it.
I love it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, if you think that's funny,
she once had a miscarriage
outside a Petco.
I still have the security
camera footage somewhere.
Peter, I'm your conscience,
Jiminy Cricket.
Ah! Bug!
Andrea, y-you set a place
for Jiminy again.
Oh... so I did.
Why?!
Why did he have to go around
telling strangers what to do?
Wasn't being a pediatric
oncologist enough for him?!
He hit on me
at your wedding.
Ah, let's see, what else?
What else? What else?
Oh, I-I got one.
I got one.
Lois tried to give CPR to
a kid at a wedding once,
and when she knelt down,
she accidentally high-heeled
her own stink hole.
Peter, your wife
is such a pig.
Oh, I don't know
about that, Jamie.
Pigs eat slop,
Lois only cooks it.
What the hell?
Peter, can I speak
with you for a second?
Oh, hang on, guys,
I got to talk to my dog.
What the hell
are you doing?
I'm just gabbing
with the girls.
You know our cycles
have lined up?
Mine's from wiping too hard.
You're saying horrible things
about Lois.
Oh, yeah,
it cracks up the ladies.
Yesterday, Karen laughed so hard
she popped a button
on her jeans.
And then she cried.
Peter, Lois
is your wife.
You should be
defending her,
not talking trash and
gossiping behind her back
like some kind of
Midwestern teenager.
Did you gals hear about Allie
Gallagher?
She let Alan Ackerman
smack her in the back
with his tallywhacker
behind the snack shack.
What?
Nobody here in Maryland
understands a single
word you're saying.
You should move
back to Minnesota.
I can't go back.
I Snapchatted
Matt Gackerack
a Kodak of my ass crack!
Hey, Lois?
I did something bad
I need to tell you about.
Peter, I know.
You used some of my magazines
for your fake ransom notes.
It's okay.
No, no, no, no,
that's not it.
But did you put the ice
cream where the guy said?
Because he will
hurt your family.
Look, the thing is,
me and my new girlfriends,
we've kind of been
talking trash about you
and laughing
behind your back.
Peter, of course
your new friends
have been talking crap about me.
That's what women do.
What?
So... you're not mad?
Well, I'm not thrilled,
but I understand what it's like
to be friends with women.
I'm sure they talk trash
about you behind your back.
They most
certainly do not!
I guarantee you that
as soon as you leave the room,
they tear you to shreds.
That's not true.
If it was, I would've
figured it out.
Just like I figured out who was
stealing my lunch at work.
Next time there's a sandwich
in the fridge
with somebody's name on it,
don't eat it, scumbag!
Please, you don't understand!
Oh, I understand.
That lunch didn't
have your name on it,
but this bullet does.
My name is Peter, too...!
Ugh, have you guys seen
the new Jessica Biel movie?
I-I don't get
what men see in her.
Um, her dumper?
I just think she's
really plain-looking.
She kind of annoys me.
You know who's really beautiful?
Joan Allen.
Yes!
Uh, stunning.
Yeah, uh... I-I think, um...
Um, I'm maybe gonna
go use the restroom
and let you guys talk about
whatever you're gonna
talk about.
Huh, I guess Peter made
it to the bathroom,
'cause I can't feel
him walking anymore.
I know.
"Fee-Fi-fo-fum!"
Right?
And what about
those drugstore glasses?
These aren't drugstore glasses,
they came from
a doctor Halloween costume.
Lois was right.
They are making fun of me
behind my back.
They're like a nasty wolf pack.
Hey, man,
just a heads-up:
instead of howling
at the moon tonight,
we're all gonna yell
"cock-a-doodle-doo!"
Really?
That seems weird.
I'm just trying to make sure
you don't look silly.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
What an idiot!
He actually believed me!
That's what a rooster says, not
a wolf!
Hi, Daddy!
How was howling at the moon?
Shut up!
Why aren't you asleep?
Why isn't he asleep?
Leave him alone!
Have you been
drinking again, Phil?
That's none of
your business!
I never wanted a cub!
Get out!
Get out now
and don't ever come back!
Hey, buddy,
want to get high?
Oh, my God. Phil?
Hey... Robert.
Wow.
Ah, hey,
listen, man...
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
"Cock-a-doodle-doo"
is a passion project
I'd been mulling over for years,
and when Family Guy gave me
the opportunity to shoot it,
I knew there was only one actor
who could portray
Phil the Wolf: Glenn Quagmire.
Peter gave me a beer that tasted
funny, and when I woke up,
I was wearing lipstick
and a wolf suit.
Lois, you were right.
Those women
were talking about me.
Oh, dear.
What did they say?
I don't even remember,
there was such a long cutaway,
but I know it was really mean.
Oh, I'm so
sorry, Peter.
So what do I do now?
Confront them face-to-face
and explain why I'm angry?
Of course not.
Being friends with women is
way more complex than that.
You need to be more
underhanded and vicious.
You and I will get revenge
on those bitches lady-style.
Really?
We'll-we'll do it together?
Yeah, it'll be fun.
Like when we watched
Battlestar Galactica together.
Now, which Cylon is that?
Ah, I-I don't know.
I think it's Number Six.
Wait, i-is that
the same Number Six
that had sex with Dr. Baltar?
I don't... I've been...
I've been watching this
the same exact amount
of time you have, Lois.
I don't know
anything you don't.
Ooh, what does that green button
on the far panel do?
How in God's name
would I know that?!
I don't know!
It's green, so it probably
makes something go.
Hello?
Peter, where are you?
I thought we were gonna
go after Becca.
Way ahead of you, Lois.
I just cut her brakes.
What?!
Don't you think
that's a little dangerous?
Hey, you're the one who said we
should try to ruin her marriage.
She bangs up her car,
her husband's gonna be furious.
What was that?
Oh, I-I just ran a red light.
My car won't slow down
for some reason.
Anyway, this is
gonna be awesome.
Geez, I'm going, like, 95.
Peter, are you sure
you didn't cut your brakes?
That's ridiculous.
Why would I cut my own...
Kids, get out of the way!
I can't stop!
All right, Peter,
next is Jamie.
Now, what's the most
important thing in her life?
Oh, that's easy.
Her daughter Emily
is a competitive diver.
The whole family's dream
is that she gets a spot
on the U.S. Olympic Team.
Okay, so get a lead pipe and
bust this girl's kneecaps.
No, no, no, Lois.
That's not how
we're gonna do this.
♪ Out on the streets ♪
♪ That's where we'll meet ♪
♪ You make the night ♪
♪ I always cross the line ♪
♪ Tightened our belts ♪
♪ Abused ourselves ♪
♪ Get in our way ♪
♪ We'll put you on your shelf ♪
♪ Round and round ♪
♪ With love we'll find a way ♪
♪ Just give it time ♪
♪ Round and round ♪
♪ What comes around
goes around ♪
♪ I'll tell you why ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ ♪
That's how we're
gonna do this.
Okay, next is Karen.
Now, she's been planning her
daughter's wedding for a year.
If it doesn't go perfectly,
she'll be crushed.
Already on it, Lois.
I bribed one of
the busboys.
He has a little surprise
planned for her.
Oh, my God!
Somebody stabbed the groom!
Oh, no,
it's not a perfect day.
Well, we got those
bitches good, huh, Peter?
Yeah, thanks, Lois.
And you were right.
Being friends with women
is way too complicated
and way too
intense for me.
Now let me just pay the busboy
and we can get out of here.
Ah! I knew he didn't
understand the plan!
Hey, guys.
Oh, hey, Peter.
Look, I-I'm real sorry
I got so worked up at my roast.
And if you're willing,
I'd like to be friends
with you guys again.
Because men might
punch you in the gut
and call you a fat idiot,
but at least they do it
to your face and own it.
You were mad at us?
Yeah, we ain't spoke
in a week.
I thought you were out of town.
People come, people go.
I didn't give no mind.
So we're-we're
friends again?
We were never not friends,
you idiot.
I love you guys.
Guys are the best.
Not women.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru